http://www.patrickarundell.com/about/data-privacy-and-cookie-policy

Subscribe
Get My App: AndroidiPhone & iPadFacebook
Data/Cookie Policy
HomeAries HoroscopesTaurus HoroscopesGemini HoroscopesCancer HoroscopesLeo HoroscopesVirgo HoroscopesLibra HoroscopesScorpio HoroscopesSagittarius HoroscopesCapricorn HoroscopesAquarius HoroscopesPisces HoroscopesHoroscope ACE AppFree HoroscopesDaily HoroscopesTomorrow's HoroscopesWeekly HoroscopesMonthly Horoscopes2020 HoroscopesFree Tarot ReadingsTarot for year 2021Tarot Card MeaningsLove Tarot Card MeaningsAbout Tarot1-to-1 Psychic ReadingsWebcam PsychicsLow Cost Psychic ReadingsPsychicsPsychic ReadingsMedium readingsZener CardsNumerologyTarotRunesClairvoyantsTarot Card Reading: Game of ThronesWebcam Psychics20212021 Solar ReturnTarot for year 20212020 Horoscopes2020 Solar Return2019 Horoscopes2019 Solar Return2019 Horoscope Videos2018 Solar ReturnHoroscope 2018Year 2017Year 2016Year 2015Year 2014Personal HoroscopesFree Horoscope ReportsLoveDaily Love HoroscopesTomorrow's Love HoroscopesWeekly Love HoroscopesMonthly Love Horoscopes2020 Love Horoscopes2019 Love Horoscopes2018 Love Horoscopes2016 Love Horoscopes2017 Love HoroscopesFREE Birth ChartVideosWeekly Horoscope VideosMonthly Horoscope VideosVideo Horoscopes 2021Video Horoscopes 2020YouTubeChineseDaily HoroscopesWeekly HoroscopesChinese Monthly HoroscopesChinese Horoscopes 2021Chinese Horoscopes 2020Year of the Rat 2020Chinese Horoscopes 2019Year of the Boar 2019Chinese Horoscopes 2018Year of the Dog 2018Chinese Horoscopes 2017Year of the Rooster 2017Chinese Horoscopes 2016Year of the Monkey 2016Chinese Horoscopes 2015Year of the Sheep 2015Year of the Horse 2014Chinese Horoscopes 2014Year of the SnakeYear of the DragonYear of the HareIndianIndian Daily HoroscopesIndian Weekly HoroscopesIndian Monthly HoroscopesIndian Horoscopes 2021Indian Horoscopes 2020Indian Horoscopes 2019Indian Horoscopes 2018Indian Horoscopes 2017Indian Horoscopes 2016Indian Horoscopes 2015Indian Horoscopes 2014About Indian AstrologyIndian Zodiac SignsAstrologyThe Vernal EquinoxFree Astrology ReportZodiac SignsAriesTaurusGeminiCancerLeoVirgoLibraScorpioSagittariusCapricornAquariusPiscesMyths and LegendsDefence of AstrologyFlowers-and-BirthstonesAstrologers' PrayerThe PlanetsThe SunThe MoonMercuryVenusMarsJupiterSaturnUranusNeptunePlutoChironPlanetary Houses1st House2nd House3rd House4th House5th House6th House7th House8th House9th House10th House11th House12th HouseRetrograde PlanetsMercuryVenusMarsJupiterSaturnUranusNeptunePlutoSeasonal BirthdaysMy FacebookMy YouTubeMy Google PlusBlogNewsAboutContact PatrickBusiness EnquiriesData Privacy and Cookie Policy
FREE Psychic Chat tap here...
Data, Privacy and Cookie Policy
Data - GDPR
GDPR (General Data Protection Regulations - EEC) as of 25th May 2018.
Patrickarundell.com My commitment to the General Data Protection Regulation Statement (GDPR)
The EU General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) replaces the 1995 EU Data Protection Directive, strengthening the rights that EU individuals have over their data, and creating a uniform data protection law across Europe. Patrick Arundell Astrology (patrickarundell.com) will comply with applicable GDPR regulations as a data controller when they take effect on 25th May 2018.
Here at Patrick Arundell Astrology (patrickarundell.com) we take your privacy seriously and will only use your personal information to provide the products and services you have requested from us.
The law on data protection sets out a number of different reasons for which a company may collect and process your personal data.
Consent
We will send you information but only with your specific consent, when you tick to opt in to our (for example) Weekly Astrology Overview and Daily Horoscopes. Please click here to see our Subscribe Page.
Third Party Sites
We at Patrick Arundell Astrology (patrickarundell.com) DO NOT sell or share your personal information to any third party or business.
Personal Horoscopes
Our Personal Horoscope Reports are provided in conjunction with a Partner StarDM. For more information on their Privacy Policy please click here...
https://patrickarundell.astrostore.net/page/privacy_policy
Privacy Policy
We at Patrick Arundell Astrology (patrickarundell.com) DO NOT share your personal information with any other parties, promotion or business.
Cookie Policy
Like other websites, we use cookies for certain parts of the site.
What is a Cookie and what do they do? A cookie is a small text file stored on your computer by your web browser.
Cookies on Patrick Arundell Astrology (patrickarundell.com)
Cookies can have many different tasks on the internet we use them for...
Statistics:
We use Googles' analytics to monitor how visitors move around our site and how visitors reached it. This is used so that we can see figures on which types of content visitors use most and how long they stayed. You can opt out of these if you want at: https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout
Third Party Social Media, Psychic/Astrology Services Partners
Social networks, video and other services we offer are run by other companies. These companies may drop cookies on your computer when you use them or if you are already logged in to them.
Registration cookies: when you register with one of our services, we generate cookies that let us know whether you are signed in or not. Our servers use these cookies to work out which account you are signed in with, and load specific information relevant to you and your needs.
Anonymous analytics cookies: every time someone visits our website, partner services or software provided by another organisation generates an 'anonymous analytics cookie'. These cookies can tell us whether or not you have visited the site before. Your browser will tell us if you have these cookies and, if you don't, we generate new ones. This allows us to track how many individual users we have, and how often they visit the site. We use these cookies to gather statistics, for example, the number of visits to a page.
Third party cookies: on some pages of our website, other organisations may also set their own anonymous cookies. They do this to track the success of their application, or to customise the application for you. Because of how cookies work, our website cannot access these cookies, nor can the other organisation access the data in cookies we use on our website. For example, when you share a page using a social-media sharing button (Facebook, Twitter or Google+) on our site, the social network that has created the button will record that you have done this.
Advertising
Advertisements on the Website are provided by other organisations. Our advertising partners will serve advertisements that they believe are most likely to be of interest to you, based on information about your visit to the Website and other websites. In order to do this, our advertising partner may need to place a cookie on your computer. These cookies hold information about the computer - they don't hold personal information about you (ie it's not linked to you as an individual).
For more information about this type of online behavioural advertising, about cookies, and about how to turn this feature off, please visit http://www.youronlinechoices.com/uk/
Please note that turning off advertising cookies won't mean that you are not served any advertising merely that it will not be tailored to your interests.
How to turn cookies off
It is usually possible to stop your browser accepting cookies, or to stop it accepting cookies from a particular website. However, we cannot tell if you are signed in without using cookies, so you would not be able to acccess your birth profiles of celebrities favourites.
All modern browsers allow you to change your cookie settings. You can usually find these settings in the 'Options' or 'Preferences' menu of your browser. To understand these settings, the following links may be helpful, or you can use the 'Help' option in your browser for more details.
Cookie settings in Chrome
Cookie settings in Firefox
Cookie settings in Internet Explorer
Cookie settings in Safari
Cookie settings in Opera
More information on Cookies
Here is a list of useful sites that you can find out more about specific services that we may use and their use of cookies:
Facebook's policy: http://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/your-info-on-other
Twitter's privacy policy: https://twitter.com/privacy
YouTube video player cookie policy: http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/faq/#toc-cookies (Google's standard terms).
Web Server Log and Traffic Analysis
Patrick Arundell Astrology (patrickarundell.com) collects IP address data regarding visitors to the web site. The IP address does not reveal any personally identifiable information about the visitor other than the IP address from which they have accessed our site.
Patrick Arundell Astrology (patrickarundell.com) may use this information to gather statistics or to initiate future improvements to the site but will NOT share this information with third parties at anytime.
Patrick Arundell Astrology (patrickarundell.com) web servers do not record personally identifiable information about the visitor.
Device information
In addition to log data, we collect information about the device you’re using to access our website, including the type of device and the operating system to help give a better experience when visiting the site.
Whether we collect some or all of this information often depends on what type of device you’re using and its settings. For example, different types of information are available depending on whether you’re using a Mac, a PC, an iPhone or Android based device. To learn more about what information your device makes available to us, please check the policies of your device manufacturer or software provider.
Please CLICK to use site to its full...
Daily Astrology & Tarot Video Show...
Talk to Patrick or Alyssa Live Please (Click/Tap Here)...
Horoscopes,
Love Horoscopes,
Psychics,
Tarot,
Chinese
Horoscopes,
Indian Vedic
Horoscopes
Resources    © 2001 - 2020 Patrick Arundell Astrology.
facebook
